Experience the horror of war
Nazi Overlord is a action, horror, mystery film directed by Rob Pallatina.
A D-Day rescue mission turns ugly when a band of Allied soldiers
battle with horrific experiments created by the Nazis.
Colonel Forrester, played by Tom Sizemore.
Dr. Eris, played by Dominique Swain.
President of the United States, played by Anthony Jensen.
Captain Rogers, played by Andrew Liberty.
Lt. Haas, played by Greg Furman.
Grey, played by Damian Joseph Quinn.
Overlord is a 2018 American alternate history action horror film
directed by Julius Avery and written by Billy Ray and Mark L.
It stars Jovan Adepo, Wyatt Russell, Mathilde Ollivier, John Magaro, Gianny
Taufer, Pilou Asbæk, Bokeem Woodbine and Iain De Caestecker.
The film was produced by Lindsey Weber and J.
Abrams, through his Bad Robot banner, as the company's first R-rated film.
The plot follows several American soldiers who are dropped behind enemy lines
the day before D-Day and discover terrifying Nazi experiments.
Overlord was released in the United States on
November 9, 2018, by Paramount Pictures.
The film received generally positive reviews and grossed
$41.7 million against a budget of $38 million.
The film explores themes of biological weapon, nazi,
world war ii, rescue mission, torture.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.